Edinburgh Fringe, which is where
I am now. I came to the Edinburgh
Fringe in 2023 and I didn't have a
venue. I decided I was going to do a
show about project management.
I didn't have a venue.
And so what I did was I started to
do shows on the Meadows, which is the
part that's just south of Edinburgh
town centre. And because like I
didn't have any constraints on the
venue, I did three shows a day that
were half an hour each and I recorded
every one so I talked three times
a day about the ideas that I was
trying to kind of grapple with and I
think my memory is that I didn't
always do the same show that I kind of
covered different subjects in
different shows because I was trying to
kind of get through the different
bits and some people that I knew so
kind of I know some people who were
in the stand-up comedy circuit in
London and they came along to see
it some people that I know from
Edinburgh came along to see it and
the result of that was that I'm kind
of starting to kind of like get
familiar with the ideas and then after
about a week um uh i'd been doing
kind of opening uh spots um for um a
friend of mine who had a topical
comedy show and um he rang me one day
and said oh i've got covid i can't
do my show tonight do you want to use
the venue and i said yes i do want
to use the venue and so i did i used
the venue that night um and um i
went in front of an audience a bigger
audience than this um that um that
um that wasn't my audience and i said
to them look,
I'm going to do a show about project
management. It's not going to be
about topical comedy. If you don't
want to stay, then that's fine. I
completely understand. But everybody
stayed. Because I've been working
through this material every day on
the Meadows, I could do the show, I
did the show,
and I got very positive
responses for it.